(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Helen had nothing to do one Saturday night.
Let's go to a drive-in theater, said
Donna.
Helen had no idea what that was.
Donna told her she would love it.
Helen agreed to go.
Drive-in theaters play movies outdoors.
People park their cars in front of a
giant screen.
They each get a pair of speakers.
Everyone watches the movie from their cars.
Helen had seen many of them in old
movies.
This is where people used to go on
dates, she said.
She had no idea they still existed.
The girls watched a horror movie.
It was scarier than watching it in a
room with a bunch of people.
They should bring these back, said Donna.